<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><biographies>
	<biography character="pingu" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_pingu.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_pingu.jpg" x="447.9" y="98"><![CDATA[Pingu

Mischievous and warm-hearted, Pingu is about as cheeky as you can get without losing any friends. Like any five-year-old, he is constantly pushing boundaries, so even the most routine activities transform into the unexpected when Pingu gets involved! Luckily, Pingu is as good at getting out of trouble as he is at getting into it and he usually manages to win everyone over with his playful nature.
Pingu is a penguin of emotional extremes. He’s full of energy, life and love. And whatever Pingu is feeling, he lets everyone know about it, blowing his beak out into a trumpet shape with a loud ‘Nug Nug!’ of triumph... or frustration.
Like any growing penguin, Pingu has a healthy appetite and has developed very well defined tastes, refusing to eat his greens (and his mother’s fish porridge!) but happily overindulging on sweets and popcorn.
You are most likely to see Pingu on his sledge, his blue pushalong scooter, or (as a treat) riding on the back of his Dad’s snowcart. He loves winter sports and is fiercely competitive! This comes from Pingu’s determination to hog the spotlight and he can get grumpy if he thinks he’s not getting enough attention!]]></biography>
	<biography character="robby" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_robbie.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_robbie.jpg" x="532.9" y="95"><![CDATA[Robby

Robby is Pingu’s best friend – and that means double trouble! With Pingu at his side, Robby lands himself in all sorts of comical situations, and they tend to egg each other on until they just tip over the edge of silliness. Robby and Pingu first met through one of their favourite pastimes – fishing.
When Pingu turned up to fish at his ice hole, Robby played a trick on Pingu, only to find him an equal match in his games and pranks.
So far in PINGU we haven’t found anything out about Robby’s background, where he comes from or who his family are. He doesn’t go to school with Pingu and we have never seen him with any other seal friends. Despite this, Robby is by no means an elusive or enigmatic character – he is very open and extremely playful.
Robby is full of energy and enthusiasm for whatever he does and is always eager to inspire Pingu to join in with his activities. He is the Stan Laurel to Pingu’s Oliver Hardy, a real comedian and very fond of practical jokes.]]></biography>
	<biography character="pinga" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_pinga.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_pinga.jpg" x="620.9" y="99"><![CDATA[Pinga

Pinga is Pingu’s three year old baby sister - she loves her big brother and always tags along when he’s around. She is not yet old enough to be fully independent and looks to her big brother to include her in his games and adventures.
Pinga is adorable and loved by all, although she is capable of throwing quite a tantrum when something upsets her.
However, her tantrums aren’t arbitrary and are usually triggered by some misadventure, like when her dad runs over her toy pram! Pinga is also very straightforward and honest and because she doesn’t always understand the consequences, will happily own up to something that Pingu is trying to cover up!
Pinga loves her toy rabbit, which she carries with her everywhere and she often carries a little bag too.
Pinga isn’t old enough to go to school with Pingu so she goes to the nursery instead. Even at the nursery, Pinga is a little shy with strangers and needs Pingu there to show her how to join in with the games. Pinga wants to grow up quickly to be just like her brother, and tends to try and get ahead of herself as a result.]]></biography>
	<biography character="bajoo" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_bajoo.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_bajoo.jpg" x="450.9" y="200"><![CDATA[Bajoo

Clumsy, snuffly and very shy, Bajoo is an adorable junior “Abominable Snowman” who, despite living in the Antarctic, doesn’t like the cold! Always wrapped up in earmuffs and a scarf, even his name derives from the sound he makes while sneezing! Bajoo makes his first appearance in the episode ‘Pingu & the Abominable Snowman’.
Determined to stay hidden from adults’ eyes, Bajoo emerges to play in secret with Pingu and Pinga, leaving only a trail of large mysterious footprints.]]></biography>
	<biography character="mother" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_mother.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_mother.jpg" x="535.9" y="202"><![CDATA[Mother

Pingu's mother can generally be found at home in the igloo and although Pingu's antics can sometimes make her cross, she is always there to give him a hug when he needs one.
Mother has infinite patience with her two children and she is devoted to them both. She is sensible in what she allows them to get up to in the igloo but understands that being a child is all about having fun. Mother loves to see her family happy and is always baking cakes and keeping the igloo in cosy order.
When she manages to find a moment to herself Mother knits, or reads the newspaper while Pingu’s father gets on with a household chore!]]></biography>
	<biography character="father" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_father.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_father.jpg" x="618.9" y="200"><![CDATA[Father

Pingu’s dad is the local postman. He delivers the letters on his snowcart, which also comes in handy for taking the family out and about, visiting the shops or Grandpa’s igloo. Father has a talent for making toys for his children and he is indispensable when it comes to DIY. Like mother, he is devoted to Pingu and Pinga and he is a very calm and solid character who can handle pretty much anything – whether it’s Pingu stuck in a snowdrift or Pinga crying over a lost toy.
A real renaissance penguin, Dad does the ironing or the knitting at home if Mother is busy and is happiest when he’s doing something practical. Father is quite capable of getting cross, but most of the time he rather enjoys having two bouncy little penguins around and is very proud of everything they do.]]></biography>
	<biography character="grandfather" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_grandad.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_grandad.jpg" x="481.9" y="311"><![CDATA[Grandfather

Grandfather lives a short snowcart trip away from Pingu’s igloo. He’s just about the best grandfather a penguin could wish for and has always got something new for Pingu to play with. Grandfather is quite old and not as fast on his flippers as he used to be. 
But when Pingu’s around, there’s a glint in his eye that tells us where Pingu gets his mischievous streak from.
Grandfather is just as likely to get into trouble as Pingu is. But Grandfather really comes in handy when Pingu’s parents are being less than understanding. A penguin of many talents, Grandfather can be called upon to teach the accordion or help Pingu fly a kite, but sometimes Grandfather relies on his family to help him too.]]></biography>
	<biography character="pingi" thumb="assets/biography_images/thumb_pingi.jpg" image="assets/biography_images/biog_pingi.jpg" x="566.9" y="316"><![CDATA[Pingi

When Pingi first arrived at her new school she was told to sit next to Pingu, who made her very unwelcome.
Despite this, she liked him immediately and was very upset when he refused to play with her after school.
When Pingu rejected her invitation to be friends, Pingi burst into tears, but her resilient side won through and by throwing a snowball in anger at Pingu, she initiated the snowball fight that brought them together. Pingi is not as adventurous as Pingu is and she will only get herself into trouble or discover new things if Pingu has dragged her into it. She is very generous and anxious to be liked by everyone she meets.
When Pingu is around, she is happy to take a backseat in the action, but when she needs to, she has a surprisingly tough nature and a great ability to stand up for herself.]]></biography>
</biographies>
